Christopher Snitchler

(248)210-0994 | chris@n30.us | Holly, MI 48442

SUMMARY

Experienced Integrated Systems Administrator with a focus on Digital Out of Home Entertainment. Drawing from a solid technical foundation and a genuine drive for crafting immersive experiences, with a commitment to guaranteeing smooth operations and fine-tuned performance of integrated systems.

Collaborated closely with the Vice President of Games & Entertainment to develop and execute a strategic vision that generated \$100 million in additional revenue over the life the Amusements Department.

EXPERIENCE

Integrated Systems Administrator, Lucky Strike Entertainment LLC, 2021 - Current Encino, CA (Remote)

Lucky Strike is a premier experiential entertainment brand. With 14 nationwide locations, 7 featuring industry-leading arcades.

- Directed the complete management of the Customer Data Environment (CDE) while concurrently leading Point of Sale operations, resulting in improved data accuracy, enhanced customer insights, and a 15% increase in sales revenue.
- Spearheaded the development and implementation of rigorous disaster recovery strategies, resulting in a 30% increase in system uptime, and a 60% reduction in data recovery time.
- Led the successful virtualization of the MICROS system, aligning with disaster recovery policy; increased system
 reliability by 60% and minimized potential revenue loss during downtime.
- Engineered a streamlined and integrated systems environment by creating, enhancing, and regularly maintaining system automation scripts, yielding a 30% increase in operational efficiency.
- Expanded the implementation of ConnectWise Automate, automating patch management tasks and decreasing patch deployment time by 60%, consequently enhancing system stability and security.
- Orchestrated the implementation of monitoring and alert systems across the Customer Data Environment (CDE), resulting in a 30% reduction in overall system downtime and enabling timely resolution of critical issues for enhanced operational efficiency.
- Launched a seamless hardware refresh project, migrating all on-premise CDE systems to state-of-the-art infrastructure; reducing maintenance costs by 40%.
- Championed the smooth migration of FreedomPay's payment system from FPPOS to FCCD, resulting in a 40% reduction in transaction processing errors and a 20% increase in customer satisfaction ratings.

Point of Sale Manager, Lucky Strike Entertainment LLC, 2017 - 2021 Sherman Oaks, CA (Remote)

- Implemented and maintained the MICROS RES 3700 systems in all 19 venues nationwide, resulting in a significant contribution of approximately \$115 million in total annual revenue.
- Achieved an outstanding 99% in-house resolution rate for MICROS support by expertly configuring and optimizing venue setups, ensuring uninterrupted service and exceptional customer experience.
- Programmed and customized SIM scripts, optimizing property-level configurations for seamless revenue center and service type setups; reducing manual setup time by 50%.
- Led the staging, configuration, deployment, patching, and system administration of all MICROS servers and terminals, ensuring consistent performance across venues.

Christopher Snitchler

(248)210-0994 | chris@n30.us | Holly, MI 48442

- Delivered comprehensive hardware and software support for 15+ venues, swiftly troubleshooting and resolving technical issues, resulting in a reduction in downtime and ensuring seamless operations.
- Designed equipment site plans for new venues, overseeing hardware deployment and system configuration/programming.
- Addressed level 1 support requests for companies' software products, including Salesforce, Tripleseat, MyMicros, custom event booking, and event deposit payment platforms.
- Pioneered the design and implementation of a comprehensive BI reporting and analytics platform, equipping stakeholders with actionable insights; optimized marketing spend by 15% and achieved a 30% improvement in operational efficiency.
- Maintained, programmed, and repaired aging A/V systems in all venues before individual venue upgrades, ensuring uninterrupted entertainment experiences.
- Served as a crucial liaison between the company and primary A/V vendor, facilitating effective communication and timely solutions.

Game Room Manager, Revel and Roll, 2016 - 2017 Ann Arbor, MI

Games & Redemption Manager, Lucky Strike / FTW, 2015 - 2016 Chicago, IL

Technical Manager, Lucky Strike Entertainment LLC, 2008 - 2015 Novi, MI

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Level 1 Duo Administrator, Duo Security 2023
- Automate Administrator, ConnectWise 2023
- Automate Service Technician, ConnectWise 2023
- AV Technologist, AVIXA 2020
- Google IT Support Professional, Google 2020

SKILLS

- Server and System Administration
- Troubleshooting and Maintenance
- Automation
- Network Security
- Network Administration
- Project Management

- Disaster Planning and Recovery
- Help Desk Support
- IT Infrastructure Management
- IT Hardware Support
- CI/CD